degreedirectory.org 2018-11-16

# Learn.org -

We are committed to protecting your privacy and promise to never spam you. Below is our policy for how the information you share is collected and used.

## Why do you collect my personal information?

We collect personal information for the following three reasons...

### #1 School Request Forms

Most schools respond very quickly to the information request forms submitted through our site. In order for a school to contact you, your phone number, postal address and email address may need to be provided. We will only share your information with the specific school you requested and/or its authorized agent. We will never redistribute, resell, or share your information with other parties.

### #2 Content Subscriptions

If you wish to subscribe to our blog, digital magazine or any of our other premium content, we may ask for contact information such as your name and email address. We may also ask about your particular interests in order to serve you the information you are most interested in. Your contact information is not redistributed, sold or shared with other parties. You may opt-out of these subscriptions for any reason or at any time.

### #3 Scholarship Applications

Scholarship applications require basic personal information such as address, phone and email to contact potential award recipients. We may also ask for personal references to verify your information and history. Only top applicants will be contacted solely for the purpose of the scholarship program. Applicant information will be never distributed, sold or shared with other parties. 

## What other information do you collect?

When you visit Learn.org, we automatically collect some temporary, anonymous information about your visit to help us improve navigation or investigate disruption of service. This information includes an IP (internet protocol) address; the date and time of your visit; and the browser software and operating system used for your visit. Learn.org uses cookies to track your visit while you are using the website. 

This website also uses third party networks to serve ads to you on other websites after you've visited our website. This practice is known as retargeting and here are the basics: we, along with third-party vendors, use first-party cookies and third-party cookies together to inform, optimize, and serve ads based on your past visits to our website. By visiting our site you are agreeing to this policy.

## How do you protect my personal information?

We use security measures to protect your personal information and to control access to it, including computer safeguards, secured files and buildings to control access.

## How do I contact you about the Privacy Policy and updates?

If our information practices change in the future, we will post policy changes on our website to notify you. If policy changes do occur, only data collected from the time of the policy change moving forward will be affected.

If you have questions we can be reached via email at [moreinformation@learn.org](mailto:moreinformation@learn.org) or you can reach us by telephone at 650-488-5017. 

Our postal address is:  
Learn.org  
100 View St. 202  
Mountain View, CA 94041
